♪ Family Guy 9x07♪
Road to the North Pole
Stewie與Brian之旅特輯"北極之旅"
首播時間2010,12,12
中文字幕:wudixny @familyguy貼吧字幕組
英文字幕:elderman@www.addic7ed.com
嗨！
Hi.
我是Ron MacFarlane,Seth MacFarlane(本片創始人)的爸爸.
I'm Ron MacFarlane,Seth MacFarlane's father.
我在這要給你們講一個故事,
And I'm here to tell you the story
講的是一個在Quahog非常特別的聖誕節.
of a very special Christmas in Quahog.
Kenny Rogers本來也應該在這的
(天生一頭銀發和銀須的他是
美國歌手作曲家演員和唱片製作人等)
Kenny Rogers was supposed to be here,
但我想他已經死了.(貌似還沒死...)
but I think he's dead.
不管怎麼說,Seth是我射出來的,
Anyway, Seth came out of my penis,
他製作了這部片子.
and now he made this.
我們的故事要從聖誕節前的Quahog說起
RON: Our story begins in Quahog just before Christmastime.
小鎮被披上了一層銀裝,
The town was blanketed with snow,
樹都被修剪過了,
the trees were being trimmed,
每個人都在整理著自己的聖誕願望清單.
and everyone was making up their Christmas lists.
Jessica Biel 和Megan Fox
(倆電影演員兼辣妹)
♪Jessica Biel and Megan Fox♪
除了襪子啥也不穿
♪wearing nothing but their socks♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
額,這是不可能滴.
Well, that's just not practical.
在墨西哥度週末
♪Spending a week in Mexico♪
還有一些黑哥們和毒品
♪with some black guys and some blow♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
噢,聽起來棒極了.
Oh, that sounds terrific.
孩子們,你們呢?
How about you, kids?
我想要一雙冰鞋
♪I would like a pair of skates.♪
然後我就可以出去滑冰了
♪Then I'd go out skating.♪
但我完全不會滑冰
♪But I really don't know how to skate!♪
哈哈!
Ha-ha!
我想要一輛全粉的雷克薩斯
♪I want a Lexus all in pink,♪
和一個不喝酒的老爸
♪and a dad who doesn't drink.♪
哦,這讓我想起了12小桶啤酒
♪Oh, and that reminds me...Twelve kegs of beer!♪
所有這些幸福願望和大量的聖誕之樂是
♪All these happy wishes and lots of Christmas cheer is♪
我今年真正想要的.
♪all I really want this year!♪
看來聖誕老人得把他自己的計劃取消了
Santa's got his work cut out for him.
噢,我們都還沒開始呢.
Oh, we ain't even gotten started yet.
我想去西班牙的海濱旅遊
♪I want to tour the Spanish coast.♪
和Michael Landon的鬼魂共進午餐(1936-1991,
美國演員,作家,導演,製片.以出演多部電視劇聞名)
♪Lunch with Michael Landon's ghost.♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪That's all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
等等.你說啥?
Wait. What?
沒啥.你繼續.
Forget it.Keep going.
Jennifer Garner在我床上
(美國演員,製片人.主演過雙面女間諜)
♪Jennifer Garner in my bed.♪
讓腦袋裡少點強硬的聲音
♪Softer voices in my head.♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪That's all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
黃色蛋糕型鈾
♪Yellow cake uranium.♪
不要問為什麼
♪Never mind the reason.♪
還有滑道,梯子和一個球
♪Also Chutes and Ladders and a ball!♪
這看起來是不是太多了點
♪Doesn't this seem like too much stuff?♪
放你的屁,這還不夠呢
♪Poo on you, it's not enough!♪
好兄弟,我給你的聖誕禮物在這.
♪Buddy boy, I got your Christmas right here!♪
所有這些幸福願望
♪All these happy wishes♪
和大量的聖誕之樂
♪and lots of Christmas cheer♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want this year!♪
我只是說這好像有點過分了
I'm just saying,it seems a bit excessive.
哦,別在發表你的長篇大論了,Brian.
(soap box,街頭或公園臨時演講台.)
Oh, get off your soap box,Brian.
這是聖誕節.
It's Christmas.
聖誕節就是要得到禮物的!
And Christmas is about gettin'!
地球人都知道!
Everyone in town knows that!
狂野不羈的日本妞
♪Japanese girls with no restraint♪
把我扼到暈眩(這個受虐狂)
♪just to choke me till I faint♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
哦,giggity!
Ooh, giggity!
鍍了鉑金的銀器
♪Platinum-plated silverware.♪
只要有一天孩子們不盯著我看
♪Just one day when kids don't stare.♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪That's all I really want for Christmas this year!♪
如果你在公共機場裡放置一顆聖誕樹
♪If you put a Christmas tree in the public airport,♪
我會在法庭上告你這個混蛋
♪I will go to court and sue your ass!♪
節日快樂(這傢伙是猶太人)
Happy holidays!
我很喜歡tinker toy
(一種只有棍子和有洞圓盤的DIY式建築玩具)
♪Wouldn't I love a tinker toy.♪
一個敲鼓的小正太
♪And a little drummer boy.♪
他可以敲他的鼓或者我的屁屁
♪He can either tap his drum or my rear.♪
所有這些幸福願望和大量的聖誕之樂
♪All these happy wishes and lots of Christmas cheer♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want this year!♪
我想要一把黃金的鬍子梳
♪I want a golden mustache comb.♪
還有一些殺精泡沫膏
(難道是DS不給他BJ才想把她開了)
♪And some spermicidal foam.♪
這是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪That's all I really want for Christmas this year.♪
我想要一把嶄新的劈起桿
♪I want a brand-new pitching wedge.♪
我想要更多的Lemon Pledge
(一種檸檬味清潔劑)
♪I would like more Lemon Pledge.♪
這是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪That's all I really want for Christmas this year.♪
我想要
♪I just want a wedding ring♪
叫Jeffrey的人結婚
♪from someone named Jeffrey.♪
我只想要一些復活節彩蛋
♪I just want some colored Easter eggs.♪
我想要藍光版的《綠野仙蹤》
♪I want a Blu-Ray of The Wiz.♪
我們不知道聖誕節是啥
♪We don't know what Christmas is!♪
但我們有個叫Gishgemfloofneer的節
(不知道啥節)
♪We have something else called Gishgemfloofneer!♪
所有這些幸福願望和大量的聖誕之樂
♪All these happy wishes and lots of Christmas cheer♪
是我今年聖誕節真正想要的
♪is all I really want this year!♪
去見聖誕老人真是讓我無比激動啊
I am so excited to see Santa Claus.
你知道讓我覺得真正美好的是啥嗎?
You know what I think is really wonderful?
在我們偉大國家的這麼多商場裡
Of all the malls in this great country of ours,
他唯獨選了來我們這兒
he chooses to come here.
年復一年.
Year after year.
你看,我是說,我..我們是哪根蔥啊?
You know,I mean,who...Who are we? You know?
我來告訴你我們是誰...幸運兒啊
I'll tell you who we are...The lucky ones.
啊奧.
Uh-oh.
哦,天啊,看這隊排的.
Oh, my God, look at the line.
媽的,我們得一輩子都呆在這了.
Damn it, we're gonna be here forever.
嘿,等等,看啊!那是Quagmire,在很前面.
Hey, wait, look!There's Quagmire, way up front.
我們可以去他那兒加個塞兒.
We can cut in line with him.
呃,等等,Stewie.他不是很喜歡我...
Uh,wait,Stewie.He doesn't like me so mu...
(sighs)
Glenn?Glenn Quagmire?
你...哇.
Wha...Wow.
你...你怎麼在這?
What...What are you doing here?
噢,你好,Brian.
Oh, hi, Brian.
和其他人一樣在等聖誕老人.
Just waiting for Santa,like everyone else.
哇,不錯,酷.
Wow, cool. Cool.
哦,好傢伙,我們就在這陪你們一起好了
Oh, man, we'll just hang with you guys here.
這小傢伙是誰?嗯?是你侄子麼?
Who's this little guy?Huh?Is this your nephew?
嘿,夥計,你來這兒看聖誕老人?
Hey,buddy,you here to see Santa?
耶.希望你今年是個好孩子.
Yeah. I hope you've been a good boy this year.
這小傢伙是我侄女Abby,你個SB.
That little guy is my niece Abby,you douche.
她頭髮短是因為她做了化療.啊噢.
Her hair's short because of the chemotherapy.Uh-oh.
因為她沒頭髮,你知道為了
Do you know how much talking it took
讓她走出家我要說多少好話嗎?
to get her out of the house because of her no-hair?
噢,天啊,我...我不知道啊.
Oh, gosh, I...I didn't know.
我...我十分抱歉.
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
哦,你感到抱歉?對..對啥?
Oh, you're sorry?For... For what?
排隊等候對你來說是個大災難
That waiting in line is such a catastrophe for you
然後你就能毀了一個
that you'd rather destroy the confidence
5歲癌症病患的信心?
of a five-year-old cancer patient?
噢,別這樣.我..我不知道她快死了.
Oh, come on.I... I didn't know she was dying.
誰說要死了?!
Who said anything about dying?!
Glenn叔叔,我要死了?
Uncle Glenn, am I dying?
不,小寶貝,你不會死的.
No,sweetheart,you're not dying.
因為我們會見到聖誕老人
'Cause we're gonna see Santa,
然後他會送你一個新的大腦
and he's gonna bring you a new brain.
滾開,Brian.
Get out of here, Brian.
給我滾.
Just get out of here.
你剛才應該用點政治,Bri.
Should have gone into politics, Bri.
現在我們隊回到隊伍的尾端了.
Now we got to go to the back of the line.
吾側那!隊伍怎麼一直不動?
What the hell!Why isn't it moving?
我咋知道.每次是同樣的情況.
I don't know.It's always the same thing.
一些小肥子坐在聖誕老人腿上一直說個不停.
Some fat kid sitting on Santa's lap taking all day.
耶,耶.然後我想要一個Charles in Charge的午餐盒
(一部美國情景喜劇)
Yeah, yeah. And I want a Charles in Charge lunch box
我想要一個Magna Doodle和一副新的Uno
(前者為磁性畫圖玩具,後者為一種牌類遊戲)
and I want a Magna Doodle and a new Uno game
因為我掉了一張"變2"的牌.
on a 'cause of I lost the "Draw 2" card.
我還想要一隻寵物
And I want a pet animal
一半毛絲鼠一半貂的那種
that's half chinchilla and half mink,
因為那一定很柔軟
'cause it'd be really soft,
然後我可以叫它chink,這就好了.
and I could call it chink,and that's okay.
天啊,商場是不是快關了?
Geez, doesn't the mall close soon?
我們在這呆了好久.
We've been here forever.
你放鬆點,行不?我們都到這了.我是下一個.
Would you relax?We're right here. I'm next.
你好,聖誕老人.
Hello, Santa.
現在,額,我們有一個小問題
Now,um,we've got a slight problem here,
因為我之前很淘氣.
because I have been rather naughty.
但你是個生意人,我也是.
But you're a business man,I'm a business man.
我確定我們可以解決...一些事的.
I'm sure we can work...something...out.
(關門去喂馴鹿,明天見)
等等.你在幹什麼?
Wait. What are you doing?
聖誕老人?你現在不能走!
Santa?You can't leave now!
嘿,等等...兄弟,夥計,
Hey,wait...Wait,buddy,buddy,
我們都排隊排了2小時了.
we've been in line for,like,two hours.
抱歉.我下班了.
Sorry.I'm done.
你想讓你的小孩坐我腿上的話,
You want your kid to sit on my lap,
在Applebee的吧檯等我.
meet me at the bar at Applebee's.
啊,真操蛋.
Aw,that sucks.
抱歉,Stewie.
Sorry,Stewie.
那個婊子養的.
That son of a bitch.
他剛才不睬我.
He just turned his back on me.
就像現實對Gary Busey的置之不理一樣.
(美國演員,出演過大量電影電視劇,
他的大牙很有特色)
The way reality turned its back on Gary Busey.
我今天看起來如何,Gary Busey?
How am I doing today,Gary Busey?
你棒極了!
You're doing great!
好!我會保持下去的!
Good!Then I'll keep it up!
嘿,把你的鑰匙給我.
Hey, give me your keys.
我要用你的車.
I need your car.
什麼?你不能用我的車.
What?You're not taking my car.
那麼,非常好.你要開車帶我的.我們走.
Very well,then.You're driving me.Let's go.
開車...開車帶你去哪?
Dri... Driving you where?
到北極去見聖誕老人.
To the North Pole to see Santa Claus.
如果那個滿身流涎,洋蔥眼的蛆餅認為
If that beslubbering,onion-eyed maggot-pie thinks
我可以那樣忽略我的話,
he can just blow me off like that,
那就有麻煩了.
he's got another thing coming.
聽著,Stewie,我知道你很失望
Look, Stewie, I know you're disappointed
因為你沒見到聖誕老人,
that you didn't get to see Santa,
但我...我不會開車帶你去北極的.
but I...I'm not driving you to the North Pole.
大家聽我說,Quagmire的侄女現在在重症監護室.
Everyone,Quagmire's niece is in the ICU.
現在,我覺得我們應該去那給他一些支持.
Now,I think we should go down there to support him.
什...什麼?是的,顯然,
Wh...What?Yeah,apparently,
商場裡發生了什麼,
something happened at the mall,
讓她情況變得惡化.
and she took a turn for the worse.
他們不知道她還剩多少時間了.
They don't know how much time she has left.
Quagmire剛打來電話.
Quagmire just called.
他很傷心.
He's really upset.
聽起來他因為一些原因不想我們去那
It doesn't sound like he wants us there
但...我們無論如何都應該去.
for some reason,but...But we should go anyway.
好吧,我們去北極.
All right,let's go to the North Pole.
就這樣Brian和Stewie開始了他們的北極之旅.
And so Brian and Stewie set off on the road to the North Pole.
嘿,你想聽聽真正的真人版放屁,
Hey, you want to hear a real live-action fart
而不是那些山寨版卡通化的麼?
instead of one of those fake cartoony ones?
我們需要換一條短褲...
(看來他屎也拉出來了...)
We're gonna need another pair of pants...
和一把椅子.
And another chair.
(歡迎來到
羅德島州,巴來維
聖誕老人之家與禮物店)
嘿,Stewie,醒醒.
Hey, Stewie, wake up.
我們到了.我們到北極了.
We're here.We're at the North Pole.
哦,啊.啥?啥?啥?
呃,北極?
Oh, uh. What? What? What?Uh, North Pole?
北極!北極!
North Pole! North Pole!
就在那!
There it is!
天啊,我之前一定睡得很死!
My word, I really must have been asleep!
啊,看看這個.
Ah, look at this.
地球的頂端,Brian.
The tip of the Earth, Brian.
好了,我們去看聖誕老人吧.
Okay, let's go see Santa Claus.
好,咱們走.
All right, let's go.
嗯,這裡真是相當的喜慶,不是嗎?
Well, this is rather festive,isn't it?
真小.
Small.
那,因為住著小精靈所以肯定小啦.
Well, it has to be small because of all the tiny elves.
啊,對.
Ah, that's right.
好.說得好.小精靈.
Good. Good point.Elves.
唷,唷,你們好啊?
MAN:Yo, yo, what's up, y'alls?
你們準備好穿上上好的北極裝了嗎
Y'alls ready to kick it in some fine North Pole gear?
Brian,為啥北極有黑人少年?
Brian, why does the North Pole have black teenagers?
呃,因為...他們來自...被Katrina颶風卷來的?
Uh... 'cause...From, uh,Katrina?
啊,當然.行.
Ah, of course. All right.
嗯,呃,那我只有一個問題了.
Well, uh, I just have one more question, then.
你認為我是個傻子?!哈?你是這麼想的?
Do you think I'm an idiot?!Huh? Do you?
聽著,Stewie,去北極是一個遙遠,危險的...
Look, Stewie, the North Pole is a long and dangerous...
你不能在聖誕老人的問題上耍我,Brian!
You can't jerk me around when it comes to Santa Claus, Brian!
這有個摩天輪,還有個人吐了!
There is a Ferris wheel here,and a guy hosing vomit!
沒人會在北極吐的!
Nobody vomits at the North Pole!
除了聖誕老人的老婆
Except for Santa's wife
因為她有飲食失調症!什麼?
because she has an eating disorder!What?
是啊,因為他想要誰就要誰,而且她也知道!
Yeah,‘cause he can have anyone he wants,and she knows that!
Stewie,冷靜.
Stewie, just pull yourself together.
不,Brian!
I won't, Brian!
現在坐回到你的嬉皮車裡去
Now you get your ass back into that hippie car of yours
然後立刻帶我去北極!
and take me to the North Pole now!
聽著,我知道你很難過,
Look, I know you're upset,
但...你為什麼不只是坐下來,
but why...Why don't you just sit down,
寫下你的聖誕願望清單,
write out your Christmas list,
然後我保證把它寄給聖誕老人
and I promise I will mail it to Santa Claus?
想都別想.
Screw that.
這根本和聖誕禮物無關,Brian.
This was never about Christmas presents, Brian.
那你為什麼一直要去北極呢?
Well,then why do you want to go all the way to the North Pole?
因為...我要殺了聖誕老人!
Because...I'm going to kill Santa Claus!
原來Stewie打算幹掉聖誕老人.
So it turned out Stewie was determined to kill Santa Claus.
他會成功嗎?
Would he succeed?
那麼,讓我們拭目以待.
Well, let's find out.
等等，你TM的為啥要幹掉聖誕老人?
Wait a minute,why the hell do you want to kill Santa?
因為那個死肥仔在商場忽略了我，
Because that fat bastard blew me off at the mall,
他應該為此付出代價.
and he shall not go unpunished.
現在,我們出發吧.我已經都計劃好了.
Now,let's go.I've got it all planned out.
我要看看他的作坊,弄幾隻馴鹿做寵物.
I'm gonna see the workshop,pet a few reindeer,
拍幾張我和聖誕老人的合影,
take a few pictures of me and Santa,
然後我要把他的腦袋爆掉,
and then I'm gonna blow his brains out,
但願他那臭婆娘也在場.
hopefully with his bitch wife watching.
這太荒謬了...我們不會去北極的.
This is ridiculous...We are not going to the North Pole.
相信我,這只是在浪費時間...你不會找到聖誕老人的.
Trust me, it's a waste of time...You're not gonna find Santa.
為什麼找不到?因為跟本就沒...
Why not?Because there's no such...
因為當你到了那,你會發現
Because when you get there,you may find out
不是你原來想的那樣,
it isn't what you thought it was,
而且我不希望你失望.
and I wouldn't want you to be disappointed.
就這?這就是你的理由?
That's it?That's your reason?
嗯,你知道,你知道你為啥一事無成麼,Brian?
Well,you know,you know why nothing works out for you,Brian?
因為你的態度消極.
Because you've got a negative attitude.
就像Eeyore.
(小熊維尼裡的驢子)
Like Eeyore.
來吧,Eeyore,我們一起去玩.
Come on, Eeyore, let's go play.
我不感興趣.
I don't feel like it.
你問什麼老這麼心情不好?
Why are you always in such a bad mood?
我菊花裡有根釘子.噢.
I have a nail in my anus.Oh.
你這麼說不公平.我不覺得我
That's not fair.I don't think I have
態度消極.我只是...
a negative attitude.I just...
我...我不認為我們走上一條有潛在危險的行程是
I... I don't think it's a good idea for us
是個好主意...
to embark on a potentially dangerous journey whe...
Stewie?
對生活說是,Brian!
Say yes to life, Brian!
我會在聖誕節的時候到家的.
I'll be home for Christmas.
婊子養的!
Son of a bitch!
那麼,你在運啥,老兄?
So,what are we hauling,good buddy?
哦,我在運一大群
Oh, I got a flock of birds
太累飛不回北方的鳥.
that were too tired to fly back north.
哇,就應該這樣做,哈,Jerry?
Boy,this is the wayto do it,huh,Jerry?
當然.想這些會讓我們變懶麼?
Sure is.Think this makes us lazy?
不,我們還保持著V型呢.
(怎麼不是SB型)
Nah,we're stillin the V-shape.
(歡迎來到馬塞諸塞州
請享受我們這兒
智力低下的女人)
(歡迎來到新罕布夏州
佛蒙特州的
壞脾氣兄弟)
(歡迎來到緬因州
我們的海灘只是些
巨大醜陋的巨石)
(歡迎來到加拿大
請保持安靜
我們正在看冰壺比賽)
這是啥?這是把奇怪的槍.
What is this?This is a weird gun.
是的.別碰它.
Yeah. Don't touch that.
噢,它是把信號槍.
Oh, it's a flare gun.
也許你應該把它放回去.
Maybe you should put that back.
我只是握著它而已.這是扳機麼?
I'm just holding it.Is this the trigger?
噢,我的上帝,Stewie,你沒事吧?
Oh,my God,Stewie,you all right?
發生了什麼玩意兒?
What the hell happened?
呃,只是一些SB的東西掉下去了.
Eh, just some stupid stuff went down.
你剛才差點被殺死!
You could have been killed!
我也差點被殺死!
I could have been killed!
看看我的車!
Look at my car!
額,你看,如果你之前帶我去
Well,you know,if you had just taken me
真正的北極見聖誕老人,
to the real North Pole to see Santa,
這一切都不會發生了!
none of this would have happened!
這...這...這是什麼?你在幹嘛?
Wh... Wh... What is this?What are you doing?
搭個車唄.
Hitching a ride.
我會一直往北直到我找到聖誕老人.
I'm gonna keep heading north until I find Santa.
Stewie,你不會找到他的.
Stewie,you're not gonna find him.
你做你想做的, Brian,
You do what you want, Brian,
但我要去北極
but I am going to the North Pole
我還要殺了那混蛋!
and I'm gonna kill that bastard!
Stewie,你把我弄到現在這該死的境地,
Stewie,you're putting mein a hell of a position here,
所以我沒有別的選擇了.
but I have no choice.
你不會去殺死聖誕老人,
You're not gonna kill Santa Claus,
因為他根本就不存在.
because he doesn't exist.
真..真..真的, Brian?
(chuckling):R... R... Really, Brian?
他不存在?
He doesn't exist?
是啊,他不是真實的.
That's right, he's not real.
哦,有趣.有趣的理論,Brian.
Oh, interesting.Interesting theory, Brian.
額,還有誰不是真實的,嗯?
Um, who else isn't real, hmm?
你準備告訴我Elmo不是真實的?
(芝麻街主要人物之一)
You gonna tell me that Elmo isn't real?
哼? 海綿寶寶?他不是真實的, Brian?
Huh?SpongeBob?Is he not real,Brian?
海...海綿寶寶不是在海底
Is..Is SpongeBob not there at the bottom of the ocean
和章魚哥打工?哼?
giving Squidward the business?Hmm?
那麼Curious George呢?
(一套兒童系列叢書主角,一隻棕色的非洲猴子)
And what about Curious George?
嗯?他不存在? 哼?
Huh?Does he not really exist? Hmm?
Curious George不是真的在
Is Curious George not really out there
用他本來應該送的
making little boats out of newspapers
報紙做小船?哼?
that he should be delivering?Huh?
多讀點書,你個笨蛋.
Educate yourself, you fool.
聽著,Stewie,如果你就聽我說一會...
Look,Stewie,if you'd just listen for a sec...
不要,你聽著,Brian!
No, you listen, Brian!
我來告訴你,你帶我去北極,
I'll tell you what,you take me to the North Pole,
如果聖誕老人不在那,我可以為你做點事.
and if Santa isn't there,I'll do something for you.
什麼?當Lois
What?When Lois does that
半夜喂奶的時候
middle-of-the-night feeding
她甚至都睜不開眼,或者都沒醒,
where she doesn't even open her eyes or really wake up,
我可以讓你代我吸一次,Brian.
I'll let you take that one for me,Brian.
你說真的?當然.
Are you serious?Quite.
好,成交了.
Okay, you got a deal.
媽的,發動機不轉了.
Damn it, it won't turn over.
太好了!連加拿大的一半都沒走到,我們就走不了了.
Great!Not even halfway through Canada,and we're stuck.
喔,你們好.
Oh, hey there.
你們的車有麻煩了,嗯?
You having some car troubles, eh?
是的,我們準備去北極.
Yeah, we're trying to get to the North Pole.
我覺得你不是來自3A的,是不?誰?
(AAA這裡指American Automobile Association,美國汽車協會)
I don't suppose you're from Triple A,are you?Who?
3A,你知道嗎?AAA.
Triple A, you know?AAA.
哦,AA,唉?是啊,我剛從AA來.
(AA這裡指Alcoholics Anonymous,嗜酒者互誡協會)
Oh,AA,eh?Yeah,I just came from AA.
不,不是AA.是AAA.
No, not AA.AAA.
是啊,就是我剛說的...AA,唉?
Yeah,that's what I said..AA, eh?
哦,所以你是3A的?
Oh, so you are with Triple A?
噢,不,那是AAA.我來自AA,唉?
Oh,no,that's AAA.I just came from AA,eh?
嗯?Stewie,我覺得他就是個酒鬼.
Huh?Stewie,I think he's just a drunk.
額,管他是不是,你能幫我們嗎?
Well,drunk or not,can you help us?
只要你們加入AA,唉?
I can if you want to join AA, eh?
不,我已經是AAA的一員了.
No, I'm already a member of AAA.
我的車需要幫忙.
I need help with the car.
噢,我知道了.嗯,看起來你們的車有點漏水.
Oh, I see. Yeah,looks like you got some water leakage.
你們可能需要一個輸水管,唉?
You might need a hose, eh?
Jose,Roberto,隨便你了...你過你那有拉丁人
(Jose與hose,eh發音類似,stewie以為他在說哪個人)
Jose,Roberto,whatever...If you've got some Latinos up here
會修車,那就太好了.
that can fix cars,that'd be great.
不,我是說,你們看起來需要一些部件,唉?
No,I mean,it looks like you need a part,eh?
額,嗯,當它被修好了,我們是可以慶祝,
(party與part,eh發音類似,他以為是要開派對)
Well,yeah,when it's fixed,we can celebrate,
但先讓我們把重要的事做了.
but let's deal with first things first.
嗯,我大概可以帶你們去個加油站,唉?
Well,I can probably take you to a gas station, eh?
你帶錢了沒,唉?我不知道,我的名字還是有點分量的,
(cachet與cash,eh發音類似,意思是證明品質優良的標誌;威信)
You have cash,eh?I don't know,my name carries a little weight,
但我不知道這有啥關係.
but I don't see how that matters here.
聽著,我們沒有足夠的錢修車,
Look,we don't have enough cash to fix the car,
而且我們正在去北極的路上.
and we're kind of on our way to the North Pole.
噢,不管怎麼說開車可到不了那兒,.
Oh,a car won't take you there, anyway.
但如果你們需要,你們可以開我的雪地車去.
But if you like,you can take my snowmobile.
真的? 你就直接...給我們車?
Really? You'd just...give it to us?
哦,當然了,加拿大人的好客就是這樣滴.
Oh,sure,that's what Canadian hospitality's all about.
如果你們需要,你們也可以拿走我所有的錢和腿.
If you like,you can have all my money and my leg.
好吧.
Okay.
我們為什麼要他的腿?
(這個腿的笑點我沒搞懂...)
Why'd we take his leg?
額,我們在他們的地盤兒,Brian...
Well,we're in their country, Brian...
我們要入鄉隨俗.
We have to observe their customs.
噢!噢,天哪.
Oh! Oh, dear.
那,至少我們這次旅行已經過了
Well, at least we're done
第一站,Brian.(與砍掉第一隻腿雙關)
with the first leg of our journey, Brian.
哈!說的真對,哈.
Ha!Damn right, ha.
Brian,你覺得我們開了多久了?
Brian,how long do you think we've been driving?
不知道,我迷路了.
I don't know, I've lost track.
另外,狗沒什麼時間感的.
Besides,dogs don't have a good sense of time.
可能是三小時,可能是3年,
Could be three hours,could be three years,
我他媽怎麼知道.
I don't (bleep) know.
恩,我們現在肯定相當北了.
Well,we must be pretty far north by now.
是啊,說的沒錯.你看...那是北極光.
Yeah,you're right.Look...There's the aurora borealis.
是啊,那邊是Boreanaz極光.
(美國演員,曾演過吸血鬼殺手布菲中的天使等)
Yes, and there's the aurora Boreanaz.
嘿.
Hi there.
北極的東西都挺美啊,嗯?
Things are kind of beautiful up north, huh?
喔,不!
Oh, no!
怎麼了?我們沒油了.
What's the matter?We're out of gas.
沒油?但是,Brian,外面好冷!我們現在怎麼辦?
Out of gas?But,Brian,it's freezing out here!What are we gonna do?
不知道.我們最好想點辦法.
I don't know.We'd better think of something.
也許我能忙幫.
Maybe I can help.
這裡北邊2英里外有間老舊廢棄的獵人小屋.
There's an old,abandoned hunting cabin about two miles north of here.
你們可以在那過夜
You could spend the night there
然後早上再繼續你們的旅程.
and then resume your journey in the morning.
謝了,David.
Thanks, David.
我想夜空裡還是有不少星星的
(與明星雙關)
Guess there are a few stars in the sky tonight.
來吧.
Come on.
快點,馬上.
Come on, now.
好吧,我們讓你一個人呆著.
Okay, we'll leave you alone.
好了,可以對付今晚了.
All right,this should do for the night.
聽著,Stewie,既然現在有空了,
Look,Stewie,now that we have a moment,
我覺得我們應該給Lois打個電話並告訴她我們在那兒.
I think we should really try to call Lois and tell her where we are.
噢,別擔心...我做好安排了.
Oh, don't worry...I've got that covered.
嘿,Lois,你這兩天可以幫我預約
Hey, Lois, would you make an appointment for me
閹割手術麼?
to be neutered in two days?
額,你確定,Brian?是啊,我確定
Well, are you sure, Brian?Yes, I'm sure.
而且不管這兩天我說什麼,
And whatever I say in two days,
別讓我說服你我改變了主意.
do not let me convince you that I've changed my mind.
哇,你聽起來對這事很認真啊,Brian.
Wow, you sound pretty serious about this, Brian.
噢,是啊.其實我有一個
Oh,I am. In fact,I have this document
法律上也這樣約束我的文件.
that legally binds me to same.
它公正過了麼
Have you had it notarized?
不.不過公證人應該馬上就到了.
No.But a notary should be here any minute.
我接到了一個要公證一份文件的電話,
I received a call about notarizing a document,
但我正和我家人在一起,
but I am spending the day with my family,
所以他們也來了.
so they are here, too.
這是我老婆Janice,
This is my wife, Janice,
我女兒,Lisa和Jane,
my daughters, Lisa and Jane,
這是Rosalyn,我女兒Jane的朋友.
and this is Rosalyn,a friend of our daughter Jane's.
她家不太好
Her family life is rough,
所以我們這就像她第二個家.
so we are kind of like a second home.
Robert!嗯,這是真的.
Robert!Well, it's true.
嗯,謝謝你能抽時間
Well, thank you for taking the time
來公證這份重要文件.
to notarize this important document.
我確定你很忙.
I'm sure you are quite busy.
是的.我們只有一點點時間
Yes. We only have a moment,
因為我們要巴士旅行去Providence和一些其他的地方.
(羅德島州首府)
for we are taking a bus tour of Providence and other places.
第二天早上,Stewie和Brian步行出發
The next morning,Stewie and Brian set out on foot
前往北極.
for the North Pole.
他們又冷又累,但Stewie下定決心
They were cold and tired,but Stewie was determined
要執行他殺死聖誕老人的計劃.
to carry out his plan to kill Santa Claus.
既然你們都在看我,
As long as I've got all you people watching,
你們有誰想要買點罐子不?
does anyone want to buy some pot?
我的上帝!
My God!
我們做到了,Brian!
We made it, Brian!
北極!
The North Pole!
看到沒? ■!就在那!
See? Boom!Right there!
我告訴過你的!
I told you!
這就是聖誕老人住的地方!
This is where Santa Claus lives!
我鄙視你!
In your face!
我不相信.
I don't believe it.
我們到了.
It's here.
說對了,我們到了!
Damn right, it's here!
現在,當你知道
Now, while you think about the fact
你永遠也享受不到
that you're never going to enjoy
Lois的夜間喂奶了,
a nocturnal breast-feeding from Lois,
我要開門了.
I shall open the gate.
這不可能是啊.
This can't be it.
這不可能是聖誕老人的作坊.
This can't be Santa's workshop.
著看起來像康涅狄格州的Bridgeport.
(此市以製造業聞名)
This looks like Bridgeport, Connecticut.
哦,啊,準備好觀眾來信了.
Oh,boy,get ready for the letters.
親愛的惡搞之家的混蛋們,
Dear Family Guy bastards,
你們他媽的以為自己是誰?
who the hell do you think you are?
我讓你們知道Bridgeport市
I'll have you know that Bridgeport
在廢棄建築物,
is among the world leaders in abandoned buildings,
碎玻璃,登上式窗子,
shattered glass,boarded-up windows,
野狗和沒泵的加油站這些方面是世界領先的.
wild dogs and gas stations without pumps.
所以吃屎去吧,猶太編劇們.
So eat my (bleep), Jew writers.
嗯,不管他玩的什麼把戲,
Well,whatever sort of trick this is,
我是不會被阻止的.
I will not be deterred.
聖誕老人不死在我手裡我是不會走的!
I'm not leaving until Santa Claus is dead by my hand!
噢,我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
你是...你是聖誕老人!
You're...You're Santa Claus!
是啊.你是誰?
Yeah.Who are you?
我是Stewie Griffin,而且我要殺了你!
I'm Stewie Griffin,and I'm going to kill you!
啊...感謝上帝!
Ah... Thank God!
什麼?殺了我!求你了!
What?Do it! Please!
讓我脫離苦海!
Put me out of my misery!
你...想要我殺了你?
You... want me to kill you?
快點!你還在等什麼?!
Come on!What are you waiting for?!
快開槍!
Pull the trigger!
呃,我不會讓你在嘴裡幹那事的.
(stewie以為他要做口活啊...)
Well,there isn't a great deal of sport in that.
噢,我的天,你...你沒事吧?
Oh,my God,are...Are you all right?
我沒事.
I'm okay.
我只是需要喘口氣而已.
I just need to catch my breath.
我...我不明白.
I... I don't understand.
我以為你應該是歡樂開心的.
I thought you were supposed to be jolly and happy.
很久以前我確實是如此.
I used to be, a long time ago.
我給小孩子們做玩具.
I made toys for little boys and girls.
我喜歡我的工作,他們也喜歡我.
I loved my work,and they loved me.
但是後來就一發不可收拾了.
But it just got out of hand.
世界人口不停的漲啊漲.
The world's population kept growing and growing.
孩子們想要更多更好的玩具!
Kids wanted more toys,fancier toys!
我們過去常常做木頭火車和布娃娃.
We used to make wooden choo-choos and rag dolls.
你有沒有試過做一個iPod?
You ever try to make an iPod?
我接到了數以百萬計的iPod訂單!
I've got orders for millions of 'em!
噢,這提醒我了...我要一個新版本的Quicken.
(蘋果系列裡的播放器)
Oh,that reminds me..I need a new version of Quicken.
看看那些我們生產產生的有毒廢料.
Look at the toxic waste we're producing.
事實上, 我覺得這些毒素
In fact, I think the toxins are taking
比近親繁殖產生了更多的傷亡人數.
even more of a toll than the inbreeding.
近親繁殖?看看吧!
Inbreeding?Take a look!
我開始的時候只有一家的魔法小精靈,
I started with one family of magic elves,
但每年我都需要更多才能不落下工作.
and every year I needed more and more to keep up.
現在他們只是病態比賽產生的的基因突變的災難.
Now they're just a sickly race of mutated genetic disasters.
他們至少有60%生下來的時候就瞎了.
At least 60% of them are born blind.
大量的工作毀了他們,
The workload destroys them,
但他們除此之外什麼也不懂.
but they don't know anything else.
後來他們基本上是憑著本能在做,當他們生命快結束時,
It's gotten so their instincts take over,and near the end,
他們只是走到雪地裡然後死掉.
they just walk out into the snow and die.
然後馴鹿會吃掉他們,
Then the reindeer eat them,
這讓那些馴鹿變成了野蠻的野生動物
which has turned the reindeer into wild, feral creatures
而且嗜吃小精靈的肉.
with a blood-lust for elf flesh.
我甚至都不為他們祈禱了.
I don't even pray for them anymore.
因為這毫無意義.
Seems pointless.
什麼樣的上帝會允許這樣?
What God would allow this?
這不在任何一首歌或者詩裡.
This is in none of the songs or poetry.
呆在這裡讓我感到恐怖!
It's a horror show up here!
你怎麼讓這些發生的?
How could you let this happen?
我?我才不會這麼做.
Me?I didn't do this.
是聖誕節乾的!
Christmas did!
帶著銀色的熱情每口鐘都會被敲響
♪Each bell would peal with a silvery zeal♪
當我們充滿了節日的感覺
♪as the holiday feeling was filling us.♪
但現在我們只感覺到害怕
♪But now instead all we're feeling is dread♪
因為聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪because Christmastime is killing us!♪
每張聖誕願望清單都越來越胡鬧
♪Each Christmas list gets us more and more pissed♪
讓我們覺得活得很寒心
♪till the thought of existence is chilling us.♪
讓我來告訴你,用你的願望清單擦你的屁股去吧
♪I'll tell you what,shove your list up your butt♪
因為聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪because Christmastime is killing us!♪
難道你看不見
♪But can't you see that♪
你的工作讓人美夢成真
♪what you do is a dream come true?♪
難道你看不見
♪Can't you see that♪
每一個微笑都讓這變得有價值
♪every smile makes it all worthwhile?♪
不, 日你
♪No, screw you.♪
這一切都是過去
♪It's all but through.♪
現在有太多的工作了
♪There's too much to do.♪
所有的美夢都成為噩夢
♪All those dreams are nightmares♪
和空白冰冷的凝視
♪and blank icy stares!♪
過去每個小精靈只是裝貨架
♪Each little elf used to fill up a shelf♪
做玩具和無私的讓我們興奮
♪making playthings and selflessly thrilling us.♪
現在他們都精神崩潰,而且就像呆在伊拉克
♪Now they're on crack,and it feels like Iraq♪
因為聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪because Christmastime is killing us!♪
每輛模型火車只是增加我們的痛苦
♪Each model train only heightens the pain♪
在如此大的工作量下,讓我們備受煎熬
♪of a workload that's draining and drilling us.♪
指尖全都在滴血,看那傢伙剛剛尿了褲子
♪Fingers all bleed and look,that guy just peed♪
因為聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪because Christmastime is killing us!♪
難道你看不到我們的觀點
♪But can't you see our point of view?♪
我們都指望你
♪We rely on you.♪
難道你看不到聖誕之樂
♪Can't you see that Christmas cheer♪
讓我們能度過接下去的一年
♪gets us through the year?♪
我的整個團隊都是遍體鱗傷
♪My whole crew is black and blue.♪
你難道還不明白
♪Can't you take a clue?♪
你可能覺得我看起很棒,但我才28歲
♪You may think I look great,but I'm 28.♪
每一聲叮噹響都是一曲安魂的喪鐘
♪Each jingle bell is a requiem knell.♪
當你覺得我們很棒的時候我們其實是在地獄做苦工
♪And while you think it's swell we are toiling in Hell.♪
看看吧,你會發現我肩上的沉重負擔
♪Take a look, you can tell as a man I'm a shell♪
因為聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪because Christmastime is killing us!♪
殺死我們!
♪Killing us!♪
聖誕節正在殺死我們
♪Christmastime is killing us!♪
因此Brian和Stewie找到了聖誕老人
So Brian and Stewie found Santa Claus,
但他並不是他們期望的那樣.
but he sure wasn't what they expected.
結果聖誕節不斷增長的需求
It turned out the increasing demands of Christmas
全都完成了但卻毀了這可憐的老頭.
had all but destroyed the poor old man.
好吧,瞧瞧這個.
Okay, look at this.
有人給了我一個可遙控的小直升機.
Somebody gave me a little remote control helicopter.
很酷吧,嗯?
Pretty cool, huh?
噢,它壞了.
Oh, it's broken.
我不知道,孩子們,他現在情況很糟.
I don't know,boys,he's in rough shape.
醫生,你必須為他做點什麼.
Doctor, you've got to do something for him.
這是聖誕前夜.
It's Christmas Eve.
聖誕節就是他的問題所在.
Christmas is the problem.
他的身體已經跟不上了.
He can't keep this pace up anymore.
如果他今晚出去,他就死定了.
If he goes out tonight,he'll die.
那,誰去送禮物呢?
Well,then who's gonna deliver all the presents?
我們.
We will.
什麼?什麼?
What?What?
Stewie,聽著,你是對的.
Stewie, look, you were right.
聖誕老人是真的.
Santa is real.
而他需要我們的幫助.
And he needs our help.
別擔心,聖誕老人.
Don't worry, Santa.
我們會確保今年會有聖誕節的.
We'll make sure there's a Christmas this year.
謝謝你,Brian.
Thank you, Brian.
你的話讓我現在感到安心.
That brings me peace in this hour.
我馬上就要去見Allah(穆斯林的真主)了.
I'll be with Allah soon.
什麼?
What?
額,嗯...他不知道他在說什麼,他神志不清了.
Uh,ye..He doesn't know whathe's saying,he's delirious.
聽著,你們最好現在就走.
Look, you'd better get moving.
好吧,Stewie,我們去把雪橇準備好.
All right,Stewie,let's go get the sleigh ready.
難道沒有人被真主什麼的嚇了一小跳麼?
Is anyone else a little freaked out by that Allah thing?
別說了,我們走吧.
Never mind that,let's just get going.
好吧, Brian.我們開始吧.
All right, Brian.Let's do this.
走啊.
Go on.
飛起來.
Giddy-up.
快點,你們這群笨鹿.
Come on, you dumb deer.
不起作用啊.
It's not working.
我覺得他們需要點誘餌.
I think they need to be coaxed.
聖誕老人說他們吃小精靈.
Santa said they eat elf flesh.
額,噢,哦,打擾一下?
Uh, oh, oh, excuse me?
呃,先生?
Uh, sir?
小精靈先生?
Mr. Elf, sir?
在嗎?小夥子?
Hello? Young man?
我... 我覺得他自己也不知道他在哪兒.
I..I don't think he even knows where he is.
你...你想要...
Do...Do you want to just...
是啊,我是說,額,我會...我想我會試著做做看.
Yeah,I mean,uh,I'll just..try and do it,I guess.
嘿.
Hey.
嘿,夥計?
Hey, fella?
額...好吧.
Um...Okay.
再見.
Bye.
嘿,Brian,看吶.
Hey, Brian, look.
那隻馴鹿正好拉了坨屎
That one reindeer just kind of pooped
在另外一隻的臉上,然後...
in the other reindeer's face, and...
然後另外一只好想把它吃掉了.
And the other reindeer just kind of ate it.
這是不是就是聖誕的魔力呢?
Isn't Christmas magical?
好,根據這張地圖,
All right,according to this map,
我們正在靠近美國的東北海岸.
we're approaching the northeast coast of the U. S.
準備好著陸.
Get ready to land.
好了, Bri,我們到了,我們的第一鎮.
All right,Bri,this is it,our first town.
我準備去那個房頂.
I'm gonna head for that roof.
我們為什麼這麼斜?
Why are we tilting?
聽著,我還沒在這玩意兒上著陸過,懂嗎?
Look,I've never landed one of these things before,okay?
你下降的速度太快了!小心!
You're coming in too fast!Look out!
好了,還不錯.
All right, this is good.
從這間屋子進去出來後再到另外一間房子上.
In and out of this house and onto the next one.
馴鹿怎麼辦?
What about the reindeer?
嗯,我們待會再把他們放下來.
Yeah, we'll cut them down afterwards.
現在我們從煙囪下去吧.
Now let's get down the chimney.
噢!你個賤貨!
Ow!You bitch!
好了,我們把禮物放到樹下吧.
Okay, let's get the presents under the tree.
好,你帶了麼?
All right, you have 'em?
我以為你帶了.
I thought you had them.
噢,額滴神啊,它們還在雪橇上.
Oh,for the love of God,they're still in the sleigh.
啊,我日.還在房頂上?
Aw, crap.On the roof?
不,它們...它們在院子裡.
No, it's...It's in the yard.
噢,我的上帝.
Oh, my God.
你走的時候沒把門鎖打開?
Didn't you unlock the door when we left?
不,你是最後一個出來的!
No, you were the last one out!
好了,我們他媽的怎麼再進去?
Well,how the hell are we gonna get back inside?
好了,找塊石頭.
All right, find a rock.
哇,哇,哇,哇!你要幹什麼?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!What are you doing?
我在放禮物啊.
I'm putting out the presents.
不是你那樣幹的.
Not like that you're not.
高的在後面,矮的在前面.
Tall in the back,short in the front.
還有小心點,老天啊.
And show some care,for God's sake.
你知道,這...這些不是那些
You know,those...Those aren't socks and underwear
消防部門捐獻給
donated by the fire department
受虐婦女庇護所的襪子和內衣.
to some battered women's shelter.
這些是聖誕老人的禮物, Brian.
Those are Santa gifts, Brian.
你知道,你...你應該...
You know,you...You have to...
等等. 你...你在幹什麼?
Wait.What...What are you doing?
你把壁爐上的整塊餅乾都吃掉了?
Did you just eat that whole cookie off the mantel?
怎麼了?它們本來就是留給聖誕老人的.我們就是.
What?They left it out for Santa.We're Santa.
是啊,但你不能把它全吃了.
Yeah,but you're not supposed to eat all of it.
你應該咬一口然後再喝一小口牛奶.
You take a bite and a sip of milk.
這樣孩子們才知道聖誕老人來過了!
That's how the kids know Santa was here!
別對我大喊大叫的.我沒吼你. 我只是...
Don't yell at me.I'm not yelling at you.I'm just...
我只是告訴你該怎麼做.
I'm telling you how it's done.
他們... 他們需要些聖誕老人來過的跡象.
They..They need some kind of indication that Santa was here.
噢,好吧,這怎麼樣?瞧著.
Oh,okay,how about this?Look.
嘿,現在他們知道他來過了.看見沒?打住!
Hey,now they know he was here.See?Stop it!
聽著,我來這是發免費禮物的!
Look, I'm here giving out free presents!
懂麼,我想吃那他媽的餅乾就吃!
All right, I'll eat the damn cookies if I want!
你知道麼?我想我甚至可以做個三明治!
You know what?I might even make a sandwich!
等等.你要去哪?
Wait.Where are you going?
我要去廚房.
I'm going into the kitchen.
我要做個三明治然後再來點薯片什麼的.
I'm gonna make a sandwich,get some chips or something.
Brian,別鬧了!
Brian, knock it off!
呃,你看看你.
Aw, man.
你個笨蛋!
You jackass!
嘿,你們他媽的是哪根蔥啊?
Hey, who the hell are you?
呃...你好?
Uh... Hello?
你們在我房子裡幹嘛?
What are you doing in my house?
我們是聖誕老人...們.
We're Santa Claus... ses.
是啊,你是聖誕老人.
Yeah, you're Santa Claus.
所以你們才破窗而入的.
That's why you broke in through the window.
我要叫警察.
I'm calling the cops.
別,別,別.我..我可以解釋.
No, no, no.I... I can explain.
我們...我們從煙囪下來,但是...我們忘了拿禮物.
We..We came down the chimney,but we..We forgot the presents.
是...事實上是...
It's... It's actually...
是一個有趣的故事...
It's kind of a funny story...
你他媽乾了什麼呀?!
What the hell did you do?!
他正要叫警察,夥計!
He was gonna call the cops, man!
你不能叫警察抓聖誕老人.
You can't call the cops on Santa.
現在幫我辦他的屍體!
Now help me move this guy's body!
啊!他還活著.
Ugh! He's still alive.
好了,把他綁起來.
All right, tie him up.
我要把這弄得像一起盜竊案.
I'm gonna make it look like a burglary.
好吧,聽著,我...我們走吧.
All right,look,let..Let's just go.
好,好.我們會走的.
Right, right. We'll go.
我要把這球棒包起來給,額,Johnny.
I'm gonna rewrap this bat for,um, Johnny.
我們把它上面他父親的血和頭髮清理掉.
Let me just clean his father's blood and hair off it.
爸爸,我要喝水
Daddy, I want a drink of water.
日
(bleep)
嘿.
Hey, there.
你好啊?
How you doing?
你是誰?
Who are you?
我是聖誕老人.
I'm Santa.
你是聖誕老人?!
You're Santa?!
你是誰
Who are you?
Dan在哪兒?
Where's Dan?
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
噢,我靠!
Oh, crap!
快,Stewie!去拿那球棒!
Quick, Stewie!Get the bat!
救命! 救命!
Help! Help!
媽咪!
Mommy!
沒事的.沒事的.
It's okay. It's okay.
Brian, 去找找看就沒有什麼膠布.
Brian,see if you can find some duct tape.
噢,我的上帝!噢,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!Oh, my God!
媽咪!噢,我的上帝!噢,我的上帝!
Mommy!Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
媽媽!
Mama!
好了,我們把這裡清理乾淨.
All right, let's get this place cleaned up.
好了,那是最後一點血跡.
All right,that's the last of the blood.
去看看有沒有別的小孩.
Go check on the other kid.
什麼別的孩子?
What other kid?
Johnny,得到球棒的那個.
Johnny, the one who's getting the bat.
Stewie,這上面只有一間臥室.
Stewie, there's only one bedroom up here.
什麼?
What?
你有兄弟麼?
Do you have a brother?
呃,那他媽誰是John...?
Well, then who the hell is John...?
噢,我的上帝,我們進錯房子了
Oh,my God,we're in the wrong house.
媽的,我們觸動了警報.
Damn it, we tripped the alarm.
Brian,條子來了.我們走!
Brian,the cops are coming.Let's go!
什麼?我們就這麼走了?
What?We're just leaving like this?
那拯救聖誕節計劃怎麼辦?!
What about not wanting to ruin Christmas?!
聖誕節已經被毀了!
It's already ruined!
這才只是一家.
This was one house.
我們已經在這呆了一個半小時!一個...
We've been here for an hour and a half! An hour and...
首先,我們不是聖誕老人.
First of all,we're not even Santa anymore.
這是次入室搶劫.
This has been a home invasion.
但是花了一個半小時了, Brian!
But an hour and a half, Brian!
還有6小時就天亮了
It's gonna be light in six hours,
我們還要去世界其他地方送禮物!
and we have to deliver to the whole rest of the world!
這只是這個街區的唯一兩間公寓而已!
There's two apartment buildings on this block alone!
難怪聖誕老人瘋了.
No wonder Santa lost his mind.
這太荒謬了!我們幹不了這個!
This is ridiculous!We can't do this!
沒人可以.這本來就不是人類能幹的!
(Brian就不是人類...)
Nobody can. It's inhuman!
好吧,快,我們離開這兒!
All right,come on,let's get out of here!
啊,媽的,馴鹿怎麼辦?
Aw, damn,what about the reindeer?
操馴鹿的蛋!
The hell with the reindeer!
看,他們在吃對方!
Look, they're all eating each other, anyway!
而且,我們也不需要他們.
Besides, we don't need 'em.
我稍微改造了下.
I made a few modifications.
抓緊.
Hang on.
那是場災難.
That was a disaster.
我都不敢相信.
I can't believe it.
我們本應該拯救聖誕節,
We were supposed to save Christmas,
但我們完全把它搞砸了.
and we completely blew it.
我們讓聖誕老人失望了.
We failed Santa.
不.不,不是我們讓聖誕老人失望了.
No.No, we didn't fail Santa.
是這個世界讓聖誕老人失望了.
The world failed Santa.
他不斷的付出付出付出,
He gives and gives and gives,
但每個人都理所當然的享受這些.
and everyone just takes him for granted.
媽的,哦...我昨晚前都不認為他是真的.
Hell,I..I didn't even think he existed until last night.
那,我們現在要做什麼?
Well, what are we supposed to do now?
聖誕節給毀了.
Christmas is doomed.
也許,我們可以做一件事.
Maybe, but there is one thing we can do.
挪開.
Move over.
Lois!
樹下面沒有禮物!
There's no presents under the tree!
什麼?
What?
噢,我的上帝.
Oh, my God.
Joe,你拿到聖誕禮物了沒?!
Joe, did you get any Christmas presents?!
沒啊!我也沒拿到!
No!Me, neither!
我拿到了8件不太好的.
I got eight mediocre things.
早上好.Quahog.
Good morning, Quahog.
今天的頭條是...聖誕老人忘了聖誕節.
Our top story today...Santa Claus skips Christmas.
全世界充滿希望的居民們今早
Hopeful citizens worldwide woke up
起床只獲得了失望
to disappointment this morning
因為他們發現沒有聖誕老人的禮物
when they discovered no gifts from Santa
在聖誕樹下.
under their Christmas trees.
當地官員有這樣的理論
Local officials are going with the theory
今年每個人都表現不好.
that everyone was bad this year.
關於這件離奇事件調查正在持續展開
The investigation continues into this mysterious...
等等!我知道聖誕節發生了什麼.
Wait! I know what happened to Christmas!
Brian?!
聖誕老人!
Santa Claus!
是的!這是聖誕老人.
That's right!It's Santa Claus.
你們現在必須聽我說.
And you've got to listen to me.
今天沒有聖誕節的原因
The reason there was no Christmas this year
是他生病了
is that this man is sick.
非常重的病.而他需要我們幫助.
Very sick.And he needs our help.
他被我們的貪婪和貪心脅迫了很多年
He's been bludgeoned by years of greed and avarice.
全是聖誕願望清單的作坊
The workload of filling our Christmas lists
讓他不堪重負.
has overwhelmed him.
而且他在這樣下去,可能撐不到明年了.
And at the rate he's going,he may not make it another year.
但我們有一個方法可以幫助他
But there's a way for us to help him.
如果我們削減一下我們的要求
If all of us everywhere can just cut back our demands
然後每年每個人只要一件禮物的話,
and ask for only one Christmas present every year,
聖誕節還是有希望的.
there may still be hope.
我知道我們生來就不想犧牲,
I know it's in our nature to resist sacrifice,
就算再困難時期也是如此,但如果不這樣,
even in hard times,but if we don't,
我們以後就再也過不了聖誕節了.
we may have to give up Christmas altogether.
好,各位,這裡是第五新聞首播,你們都聽到了.
Well, folks, you heard it here first on Channel Five News.
看起來我們還有一個選擇
Looks like we have a choice.
那就是每人聖誕節只要一件禮物.
One Christmas gift a year for each one of us.
我們能忍受這樣麼?
Can we live with that?
我可以.
I can.
我也是.
So can I.
我也可以.
Me, too.
我也是.
I can, too.
我可以忍受的.
I can live with that.
算我一個.
Count me in.
一個就夠了.
One is enough.
是啊.
Aye.
我可以.
I can.
一個禮物可以.
One gift is okay.
我可以忍受.
I can live with it.
好,就一個.
Okay, just one.
但如果是個健身房會員,
But if it's a gym membership,
有人就要挨揍了.
somebody's getting punched in the (bleep) face.
我們可以擺脫混亂
♪We can get out of any mess♪
只要我們索取的更少
♪if we learn to live with less.♪
如果有了聖誕老人的愛我們將無所畏懼
♪And with Santa's love there's nothing to fear.♪
所有這些幸福願望和大量的聖誕之樂
♪All these happy wishes and lots of Christmas cheer♪
是我今年真正想要的!
♪is all I really want this year!♪
中文字幕:wudixny @familyguy貼吧字幕組
英文字幕:elderman@www.addic7ed.com
(打嗝)
(burps)